Index's perfect memorization isn't a life-threatening condition even if her memories aren't erased in one year periods.
That means The Church lied to Stiyl and Kanzaki?!
Successfully constructed the most effective weapon against the intruder.
Now initiating local weapon, "St. George's Sanctuary".
Proceeding to destroy intruder.
Right, I forgot to ask one thing...
...the reason why a non-esper like you...
...can't use magic...
No way...
Why can she... use magic...
Isn't it obvious?!
That Index can't use magic... was simply The Church's lie!!
Yeah, that's right!
And the fact Index would die if her memories weren't erased in one year periods is a big fat lie, too!
Her brain is just filled with The Church's magic!
Erase all that and there wouldn't be any need to erase her memories anymore!
Think about it!
Did you think...
...those people that forced her to take on the harsh role of being the index of prohibited books...
...would kindly tell lower level members like you the entire truth?!
If not, then ask Index personally!
St. George's Sanctuary does not seem to be effective against the intruder.
Switching to other spells and proceeding with the destruction of the intruder.
Fortis931!
I don't need a vague possibility.
If her memories are erased, then at least she'll still have her life.
I'll kill anyone for that.
I'll destroy whatever is needed.
That was my choice.
One that I made long ago.
"At least", huh?
That's wrong; screw that kind of pathetic thinking!
Just answer me one thing, magician!
Don't you want to save Index?!
You guys have been waiting for this, haven't you?!
A method where you don't need to take away Index's memories...
A method where you don't need to be Index's enemies...
A method where everyone is smiling and that everyone wants...
...that leads to the best happy ending!!!
You've been waiting all your lives for this, haven't you?!
For this development?
What have you guys been clenching your teeth all this time for?
Didn't you swear you'd save this one girl with your own hands?
You'd like to be the main characters of the story, too, right?!
Quit being content staying a side character!
Didn't you want to put your lives on the line and protect this one girl?!
Then, it's not over yet!
It hasn't even begun!
Quit getting depressed in this kinda long prologue!
You can reach her if you stretch your hand out!
Let's get this thing started already, magician!
Salvare000!
What's... this?
This is... Dragon's Breath!
It's akin to St. George's dragon's attack according to legend.
If you even come in contact with one feather, you'll be doomed!
Innocentius!
Go, esper!
Warning.
Chapter 6, Verse 13.
Confirmed new enemy soldier.
Changing battle logic.
Commencing search trace of the battlefield.
Complete.
Prioritizing the destruction of the most problematic enemy, Kamijyo Touma.
Warning.
Chapter 22, Verse 1.
Succeeded in reverse engineering of flame spell.
Confirmed to be a distorted interpretation of Christian doctrines, described by runes.
Constructing an anti-Christian weapon.
Moving St. George's Sanctuary to Stage 2.
Eli Eli Lama Sabachthani?
"My God, my God, why have you forsaken me?" (Matthew 27:45-46)
Innocentius!
God.
If this world really is functioning through Your system...
...then...
...I'll destroy that illusion first!!!
War... ning...
Final Chapter... Verse... 0...
"Necklace"... suffered fatal destruction...
Regeneration impo-
A mysterious ray of light and one surveillance satellite destroyed...
You and two others that don't possess any ID came into this city, apparently.
So, you guys don't have anything to do with this?
I don't know.
That letter seems to be from the other two.
Wait, I think that it's not for you, but for that kid.
It's all right!
"Salutations are worthless so let me skip that."
You've really done it, you bastard.
...was what I wanted to say...
...but if I really voiced out my personal emotions, even cutting down all the trees in the world...
...wouldn't make enough paper for that purpose, so I'll refrain from that.
As the least of courtesy I can show for your assistance in all this,
I'll explain the complete situation concerning you and her.
The English Purist Church wished to immediately take her back,
but when we asked for an explanation for lying to us,
they suddenly decided to maintain the current status quo.
I'm pretty sure it's more accurate to say they want to monitor developments.
Me, personally, I can't tolerate any second you're around her.
By the way, this doesn't exactly mean we're giving her to you.
We will collect information and retrieve her once we have gathered proper equipment.
It's not my style to kill you in your sleep...
"...so clean your neck and wait for us."
A rather extreme friend you have there.
I wonder if he mixed in some liquid explosives.
It'd be faster if you'd go see that kid in person.
That's what I'd like to say.
Well, it'd be rude to be shocked when you do see him,
so let me give you a quick and dirty lesson #1.
Yes?
Touma.
Umm...
Did you come to the wrong room?
That's memory destruction, rather than memory loss.
Memory destruction?
He didn't forget his memories,
but rather his brain cells were physically destroyed.
I don't think he'd remember anything to begin with.
Geez.
Did they open up his noggin and use a stun gun on him?
Umm...
Are you okay?
You seem to be in great pain.
No.
I'm okay.
Of course, I'm okay!
Umm...
Do we know each other by any chance?
Touma, don't you remember?
We first met on the balcony of your student dormitory.
I lived in a student dormitory?
Touma, don't you remember?
My Walking Church got destroyed by your right hand.
What's... a walking church?
Some kind of walking club?
Touma, don't you remember?
You fought against magicians for me.
Whose name is Touma?
Touma... don't you remember?
Index...
Index... loved you, Touma...
Sorry, what's index?
I'm sure it's not a person's name...
Did I have a pet dog or cat?
JUST KIDDING!
You fell for it!
What are you getting all emotional for being called a dog or cat?
You must be that type.
You like collars?
Are you requesting me to do that kind of stuff?
Huh?
Touma, weren't your brain cells blown away?
Didn't you forget everything?
You sound as if it'd be better if I did forget everything, yo.
Huh, but...
According to that frog-faced doctor,
my brain cells got destroyed, right?
That's why I should've lost my memories, right?
"Should've"?
See?
The damage was caused by magic, right?
Then, it's easy.
I touched my head with my right hand...
...and directed Imagine Breaker towards myself and voila.
Imagine... Breaker?
The name for this.
That's what the doctors called it.
In simple terms, before the damage reached the brain,
I just needed to dispel the magical damage, that's all.
And look at you...
For all the problems you caused to others this time,
you can take a good long look at yourself in the mirror, right?
Huh?
Wow, this is a mess.
I was going to die... really...
But, was that okay?
You really don't remember anything, do you?
I told you word for word what I heard from those two.
I... just didn't want that girl to cry...
That's what crossed my mind.
I don't know what this emotion is,
and I'm sure I won't ever remember anything.
But that's what crossed my mind.
Perhaps, I still remember.
Your memories are dead, along with your brain cells.
No information remains in your brain, or should, at least.
Then, where are your memories?
That's easy...
My heart, no?
Two weeks have passed since the interruption of communication with artificial satellite, Orihime-01,
yet there is still no indication as to when communications will be restored.
It has been decided the board will have immediate discussions concerning future goals.
Stiyl Magnus.
Every single person that comes here looks at how I am...
...and reacts in the same way.
"There shouldn't be a need to let a human do something machines do," right?
Yes.
General Superintendent Aleister.
I believe you already know the reason for being recalled from England.
The situation has become complicated.
"Deep Blood", correct?
Its existence is uncertain.
A girl possessing the power to kill "a certain organism", whose existence is not even certain, is being imprisoned.
What has complicated matters is that you magicians,
who shouldn't be within this city, have taken part in this.
Magicians?
It is rather easy to terminate a magician or two.
That is not the problem.
The issue is that we, the science side,
will end up defeating the magicians.
Because the science side and the magic side both hold their own exclusive technologies,
the balance of the world exists.
It is rather obvious what would happen if Academy City, which governs all espers,
insists that it has defeated magicians, no?
I see.
If I, a magician, take out someone from the magic side,
no one would have a problem with that.
Correct?
And I also possess a natural enemy of magicians.
Imagine Breaker...
But is it not dangerous to be using an esper?
There are no problems.
He is Level 0.
A "powerless" person.
He does not possess any valuable information.
There are no fears that our information would be leaked by him accompanying you.
You're telling me... to partner up with that kid?
He knows your technology,
but has no intelligence to re-create it.
Therefore, you don't have to worry
that your information might be leaked.
Understood...
But...
...does "Deep Blood" really exist?
If it really does exist, then that means...
...that the "certain organism" that it needs to kill also exists...
Vampires...
I believe occult affairs are not
our area of expertise, but yours.
Well then.
If Deep Blood proves the existence of vampires,
then whose existence will the Imagine Breaker prove?
The Alchemist, Aureolus Izzard's target, the Deep Blood...
That girl being imprisoned in Misawa cram school is...
Huh, magician?
Next time, "Science Worship".
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!